Strahinja Cokić

Personal Profile

I'm a self-taught front-end developer. I have been working with developers throughout the last couple of years and I realized that I love designing and creating beautiful experiences for the users!

I have since then worked on my design and frontend skills! I love working with HTML and CSS, I can handle a bunch of JavaScript. I am currently learning React and Redux so that I can level up my skills and be able to work on big projects. My goal for the future is to become a great frontend developer and I'm eager and ready to learn as much as possible. I am enthusiastic about learning new stu that will help me become a better developer!

Development Projects

strahinjacokic.com

I made my portfolio website from scratch with pure HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Demo

GitHub

Marvel Heroes Cards

Simple React app that uses Marvel's API to render a paginated list of Marvel comic book heroes.

Demo

GitHub

To Do App

Simple to do app built with pure HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that stores tasks to local storage.

Demo

GitHub

Two Player Dice Game

During the JavaScript course, I made a two-player game of dices where the goal is to reach 100 points.

Demo

GitHub

WordPress Projects

pobedimoastmu.rs

I created a brand identity and social media design and built a WordPress website for this NGO.

Live website

digitalnakancelarija.rs

I built a WordPress website to showcase my work related to WordPress website building.

Live website

medana.rs

I built an e-commerce website by using WordPress theme builder with automated emails.

Live website

Personal Info

strahinjacokic.com

n linkedin.com/in/strahinjacokic

github.com/scokic

+381 62 585 775

strahinjacokic@gmail.com

Tech Stack





CSS



HTML

JavaScript

*

React



Sass





* Currently learning and getting comfortable with

Redux

Work Experience

Jul 2019 – Jul 2021

Group Project Management Specialist @ Sport Vision Group

- Leading and managing two IT projects e-commerce & SAP projects
- Reporting and presenting plans and results to top management
- Managing stakeholders expectations
- Researched, implemented, and educated colleagues about the use of the Smartsheet tool
- Maintaining project plans, task lists, risk registers, and other relevant project documents
- Facilitating workshops with business representatives, partners, and consultants

Apr 2018 -Jul 2019

Business Development Manager @ Teodesk - SaaS Startup

- Created UI mockups for new features and communicated them with the developers
- Assisted in backlog management and selection of new features (Azure DevOps)
- Continuously tested the beta software in search for bugs and UX improvements
- Presented the product at corporate events and sales pitches
- Coordinated company preparation for GDPR compliance and ISO 27001 certication
- Analyzed and implemented CRM strategies across the company (HubSpot CRM)

Jun 2017 -Dec 2017

Data Collection and Labeling Associate @ MDCS

- Collected and labeled relevant data samples
- Evaluated features of internally used tool for data collection and labeling
- Trained newly recruited junior labeling associate

Oct 2016 -Mar 2017 Field Marketing Intern @ Air Serbia

Oct 2014 -Nov 2014

PR Intern @ Executive Group

May 2013 -Feb 2014

Marketing & PR Manager @ AIESEC Serbia

Education

Oct 2012 -TBD Faculty of Economics, University of Belgrade

Trade Management & Marketing

Sep 2008 -

High School of Retail

Jun 2012 Commercial Technician

Design Tools







Illustrator

Adobe XD

Designer

Skills & interests



Languages

Serbian / Native speaker
English / Advanced - C1

Competitions

ESTIEM - Case Study ShowFirst place at Air Serbia
Business Case

AIESEC - Case Challenge
Finalist on IDEA Business Case